<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>F3 SOIL</title>
    <link>https://f3soil.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on F3 SOIL</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 07:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://f3soil.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Nomad</title>
      <link>https://f3soil.com/locations/nomad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 07:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://f3soil.com/locations/nomad/</guid>
      <description>AO Nomad is a unique AO which is focused on providing the option to Ruck, Run, or Ride. All three options are by their nature activities which span significant distances and so it seemed fitting that perhaps the AO was not locked to a particular location but to the network of MCT Trails that weave across our counties. AO Nomad will have a regular schedule but will “make camp” across a series of trailheads:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tower</title>
      <link>https://f3soil.com/locations/tower/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://f3soil.com/locations/tower/</guid>
      <description>The Tower will launch on Saturday May 6th as the first AO in the Marion/Carbondale area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prost</title>
      <link>https://f3soil.com/locations/prost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 20:27:34 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://f3soil.com/locations/prost/</guid>
      <description>Was is das?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Black Forest</title>
      <link>https://f3soil.com/locations/black-forest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 20:27:34 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://f3soil.com/locations/black-forest/</guid>
      <description>Can you pronounce Bolm-Schuhkraft Park? Well, it&amp;rsquo;s a sprawling 44.5 acres park and is also known as City Park but we in F3 call it &amp;ldquo;The Black Forest&amp;rdquo;. It&amp;rsquo;s a perfect place for your morning workout!
The Black Forest is well stocked for an F3 mother-of-all beatdowns. It&amp;rsquo;s got benches and picnic tables, 4 pavilions with tables (really useful on those wet, dreary mornings), basketball courts, batting cages, exercise stations, horseshoe pits, a 1 mile paved trail, roller hockey rink, sand volleyball court, sports fields, tennis courts, and more!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Mine</title>
      <link>https://f3soil.com/locations/mine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 20:27:34 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://f3soil.com/locations/mine/</guid>
      <description>The Mine is located at Drost Park in Maryville, IL which features a seven-acre lake, several pavilions, about three miles of asphalt walking trails, picnic tables, benches, playgrounds; everything a Q needs to run a perfect boot camp workout.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Outer Rim</title>
      <link>https://f3soil.com/locations/outer-rim/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 20:27:34 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://f3soil.com/locations/outer-rim/</guid>
      <description>The Outer Rim was the first Southern Illinois AO at the ninety-acre Moody Park (f.k.a. Longacre Park). There is a huge array of amenities to provide a different beatdown, every single time. Workout Q&amp;rsquo;s have plenty of opportunity to get creative with their workouts!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Station</title>
      <link>https://f3soil.com/locations/station/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 20:27:34 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://f3soil.com/locations/station/</guid>
      <description>Right in the middle of the Metro East, O&amp;rsquo;Fallon is the perfect place for a beatdown! The community park is located in the center of the community, which means easy come and easy go. Join us in the gloom as we keep giving it away in the Metro East.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Stomping Grounds</title>
      <link>https://f3soil.com/locations/stomping-grounds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 20:27:34 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://f3soil.com/locations/stomping-grounds/</guid>
      <description>Just because workouts are held at Bicentennial Park, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean all exercises require 200 reps. But don&amp;rsquo;t be surprised if 200 makes a few appearances here and there. With plenty of amenities like nature trails and even disc golf, beatdowns are sure to be creative here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Store</title>
      <link>https://f3soil.com/locations/store/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 20:27:34 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://f3soil.com/locations/store/</guid>
      <description>You don&amp;rsquo;t go to The Store to get new clothes, just a good old-fashioned beatdown. The Store has hillside terrain, basketball courts, a sand volleyball court, and more. You may even run into a deer or maybe even Bambi&amp;rsquo;s wife. BTW, do not park on the front-right spots!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Zoo</title>
      <link>https://f3soil.com/locations/zoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 20:27:34 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://f3soil.com/locations/zoo/</guid>
      <description>The Zoo is located at Tri-Township Park in Troy, IL which does actually feature a zoo. There is nothing quite like a deep CoT being interrupted by a donkey&amp;rsquo;s bellow; come check it out for yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcements</title>
      <link>https://f3soil.com/announcements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://f3soil.com/announcements/</guid>
      <description>Special Announcements Rocky Top&amp;rsquo;s daughter, Kaila, has begun a women&amp;rsquo;s group modeled after F3, codenamed F4. They currently meet at 06:00 at several locations throughout the week. If any women in your life would be interested please reach out to Kaila at kailayoung03@gmail.com or to Rocky Top to get them connected; they use Discord instead of Slack. Highlighted Events August 1-15 Stableman 6 | Middie Mayhem August 20-26 The Covering House 24,901-Mile Challenge (Join the &amp;ldquo;F3 SoIL&amp;rdquo; team during registration.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
